Erol BicerNuclear Engineer



- **** +82-10-7497-0705
- Seoul, South Korea
- **## 1989.09.29**
- in LinkedIn
- R^G ResearchGate

LANGUAGES

English
Turkish
Korean

SYSTEM CODES

RELAP5
SNAP
GOTHIC
MARS-KS
SPACE
CAP

CFD CODES

PROGRAMMING CODES

GENERAL SOFTWARE

DOS

UNIX

CATIA

OriginLab

ParaView

MS Office

Mathcad

PROFILE

Throughout my academic and professional career, I have focused on nuclear safety analyses at the plant, system, and component levels utilizing system safety analysis and computational fluid dynamics codes. I have experience with various baseload nuclear power plant technologies as well as small, and micro modular reactors.

EDUCATION

Nuclear Engineering, Ph.D., Seoul National University

2017 – present | Seoul, South Korea

Nuclear Power Plant Engineering, M.Sc., KINGS

2014 – 2016 | Ulsan, South Korea

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Associate Manager, FNC Technology Co., Ltd. ☑ 2016 – present | Suwon, South Korea

R&D Engineer, Bil-Plas Industry and Trade Co., Ltd. ☑ 2013 – 2014 | Ankara, Turkey

CERTIFICATES

Modelling and Computation of Multiphase Flows

Swiss Federal Institute of Technology (ETH)

International Marketing, Business Knowledge and Intelligence
Ankara Chamber of Commerce (ATO)

AWARDS

International Atomic Energy Agency Fellowship, IAEA

Full Academic Scholarship, KINGS

MAIN PROJECTS

[PCCS] Conceptual Design and Development of Passive Containment Cooling System for APR1400

[SMART] System-Integrated Modular Advanced Reactor Passive Containment Cooling System

[SMR] Small and Micro Modular Reactors Technology Analyses

[PGSFR] Prototype Gen-IV Sodium-Cooled Fast Reactor Condition Analysis Project

[PAFS] Passive Auxiliary Feedwater System Development

[ATLAS] Determination of ATLAS Heat Loss and Improvement of MARS Input Model

[EUR] APR1000 PAFS Standard Design Development and EUR Certification Support

More information can be found here **2**

PERSONAL VENTURES

Nuclear Industry Association of Turkey, Board of Directors ☑

Turkish Chamber of Commerce in Korea, Co-Founder ☑

Liviboard, Co-Founder

Hacettepe Rugby Club, Founder 🖸